to align with what he has said we are
in covid solutions really before the
manif say that our mindset should
be one stop shop no one stop shop so if
you have individual clients what
potential you can still get no
and that's what we think that's what we
try to do no make you guys um reminded
of that that we are not just ending with
individual no as I said earlier
this is really a door opener this is really
the purpose of portfolios
in manulite but I don't want to
discuss all of them because pretty soon we
will be having our road show where
we can tackle that in more detail but for
now I just be focusing on the group life
insurance why is this what
sir said earlier this will penetrate you
get all the information
you can get later we will talk about
that but he said I said
it is really a door opener because one,
you will have a very good relationship
with the HR, with our product, with
group life insurance.  That's the
first thing you actually talked about.  Said
president and all, no.  So once you have
that initial step, put on the door,
everything will just simply flow
naturally, right?  That's all,
we need to keep an open mind.  So
you guys stop because sometimes in manual
life, sir says, "If you're not defeated, you stop
right away, right?"  Okay.  So please let
me on WhatsApp.  As I said earlier,
what's really in it when you
sell or engage with your
corporate clients?  Pardon the word
corporate clients, but in reality,
that could be small.  Of course we can go
through large ones, but when I say small ones, you
see a lot of them here in Tomas
Morato, right?  There are so many of them,
even the simple ones there
may be small, right?  It may be small but
sir is right, it has an owner, let's not
underestimate it, it's just a miltihan, there's no money,
that's not true.  There are so many
successful stories in Corpsol, a
very small company, but you're right,
the owner was sold, the wife
and children became MDRT, so
let's not belittle it, because the
business is small, probably the business is small, there are so
many, so we
have one particular FA, you know what
he's targeting, all the loners,
right? The
loners are just small. The ones who are swindling are just small,
but how many are they?  So
again, let's not underestimate that
because it's a door opener for individual
leads.  I said earlier,
why would he be a door opener?
Because you get so much information
about the employees.  No, what is
this information?  Which of you, when it comes to
individual insurance, what is the crucial
information for you to say that the
person you know has the capacity to
sell it?  What is the
critical information that you need?
Just one.  What is it, aunt?  What is it?  What's
that saying you shouldn't
stop it, don't stop it.
Put it out there,
maybe it will come out to others.
Okay.  What is the clinical information
for the individual?
Income.  Okay.  Do you know that
you get that in corporate?
You get that information.  Why?
Because some companies
have salary based coverage.
So when I say salary base, you will get
the name Oh, Juan Dela Cruz
his monthly income is Php1,000.
Yes.  What else?  What other information
should we get?  Critical for you.  So
tell the individual that he or she is important
to you.  You get that same information
at corporate.  What else?
What other information is very, very
good for you to get
leads?
Huh?  Work.
Work.  That's right, right?  So the same is true.
When you get the masterlist,
you'll know.  Ah, Maria, she's the
SVP for marketing.   There's
probably money in the title alone
.  No, maybe not.  I mean, there's money in the title
alone.  Okay.  Why is he
becoming a door opener?  Let me highlight
on that one.  Because once you have that
relationship with the HR,
Sir Ogu can say, can I be
there?  Can I nest
there?  Do you know about nesting?  You will be invited
to sit in their office.  And I
have seen that in several of our agents
they were allowed to do that.
They are really sitting there.  So
they were booting, we had a stand-by, they were there for
a day or two.  No financial wellness
showed up, just standing there.
Brochure no.  So,
he's really an opener because of your
very good relationship or even if it's
not very good, as long as
you have a relationship, you've already used
that.  No?  And that's what
we shouldn't forget.  Why do I say
we should not forget?  Because more
often than not, sometimes our agent
in manual life only thinks that
I have released a proposal for the
corporate account but he doesn't
follow up on it with the individual.  Next, it
increases your commission in PC.  Of
course, sir, I said earlier that
you shouldn't underestimate me.  We have
agents whose commissions are actually men
.
I have one private account.  You know, we've had it
since 2009.
Imagine the standard commission is 12%
.  Standard commission for
group.  So since 2009 it's been growing and growing
and growing.  So now it seems like
the premium is generating 100 to 1 million.
So 1 million 1% because the
company is growing and then that's it, it
gives you passive income.
You don't have anything else to do, do you?  Hi hello
madam here again.  Let's go.  You
just earn it naturally.  And then
we also counted that in MDRT.
MDR is counted in MDRT in all of the
in all of
Manul's other promotional campaigns.  And I think that's
one thing that we're very proud of because
from what we understand, other life
insurance companies don't include
corporate accounts production.   That's
not true, even though I've already got a
big account, he's not included.
But for us, he is mirrored in almost
all of Manuel Light's promotional campaigns
.  And don't worry, we have our
own promo on top of everything
else.  So maybe you saw the
groceries.  Wow, the past few days have been
full blast.
Of course I can't say no, but so far
unofficially there will be two coming from
zone one.  Oh, right?  So on top of
everything you get commission,
bonuses and all.  And then the
corporate solutions
team has its own promotion.  So what more can we ask for?
Okay.  So are we clear on why you
should never forget?
Why should you never forget?
Sir Ogon said earlier, of course when I
entered, he said, "Just Julie, let's just
keep going. Of course he
thanked me for being here."  No.  But one
thing he said is that we won't stop
until it's not in our DNA, right?  And
that's good with this particular team
because you are intentionally making it
part of your DNA.  And if that would
really happen, we assure you, it
would really propel the success because
it doesn't stop from having or
issuing proposals but that's it, you
really get so much information
because you know,
for example, you know where
their office is.  Hey, we're in BGC,
we're in Makati, let's go to HR and
then you get all the employees master
list.  When it comes to the
employee masterlist, all their employees, you
get their names, you get their birthdays
and sometimes, I said,
you will be given a salary sometimes.
And I think that on that birthday you
immediately know if it's insurable, right?  Yes.  Oh, birthday
alone.  And Auntie said earlier, did
n't she, income would really give you so
much idea that I could penetrate this
employee.  No?  So let's move on
to the next engagement
you'll have.  So that's financial wellness,
booting, nesting, that's it.  But
of course, we offer the other products
of the corporate solution.  Sir said
earlier that it was okay in our first approach, the
owner didn't want to
talk to us. Can I get
Joy Joy Joy I don't want to talk to you right now,
I'm busy, there are a lot of people like that, or the VP
for HR, sorry Joy, I'm busy now,
okay next year, but when
Joy said Madam VP for HR, I understand
you're busy now, but how about your
employees, are they covered with group
life insurance,
suddenly there's nothing, oh,
we already have a door opener, so we became a door
opener because you said he didn't want
to meet, I don't have time, Joy,
I'm busy, I'm going to
Europe for Christmas,
okay, madam, that's okay, but it's
January 1st, you might want to
consider the lives of your employees.
Exactly for renewal.   It's
for renewal, so there is one.  That's why
he becomes a door opener because
we are looking for where we
can enter.  So these are
our different products.  Again I will
not discuss everything because again
very soon I will be coming back for our
road.  And when I say very soon, maybe in
January I'll be here again.  January or
February, right?  So these are
our many products.  You have so many
products that you can use,
we will be sending all the materials to
all those who have registered.  So I
think everyone did Miss Pino.  So we'll
be sending everything.  You don't
need to take a picture of this?  You don't
need to take pictures.
You don't need my picture,
we will provide that
everything, we will provide everything.
So again as you can see at the core of
corporate solutions manual life team or
we have different kinds of products for
students or lending institutions but for
those who doesn't know yet what is
group life insurance
ah so we have package and customized so
basically here we engage with all
when i say all as long as
they are legitimate business they don't fly by night
no so whether small that we offer life
insurance yearly renewable term because it's
new maybe others not familiar no when
i say yearly renewable term every year
they need to renew with us
so that's why sir said earlier that
you can get commission on an
annual basis no so we engage with the hr
of the companies for the employees to be
covered
fyi p sigo the first time just
heard of group life insurance for
what first time so everyone knows sure sure okay
okay do
you know that because of the
pandemic all the work has brought to you
know the the need for group life
insurance so now in real life it's
easier to discuss that
no if earlier sir said that for
children if it's easier for you  When discussing pre-
pandemic, there were still some things that I didn't like,
not our media, that wasn't my
priority, but because of the
pandemic, the
mindset of HR people has really opened up more that group life
insurance is very, very important for
their employees'
coverage.  So that's what
group life insurance means, right?  So we've got
a package and customize.
Our package you can cover you
can offer this to small as five
employees.
So five employees you can offer even
to five employees.  So this is really a free
package.  So our target market
here is the small ones,
5 to 200 employees.  And I assure
you there's so much here.  This is cheaper
in the QC area, right?  Let's just try it out,
I don't know if we can
get 5 to 200. I said
earlier that all the military are included in that,
all the barber shops and salons are included in
that, so if you have somebody you know,
offer this and it will make
you activated. It's a
small amount for now, but again, I said,
let's not stop from just simply
closing the entity.  Next is hey, how is
the owner?  It's impossible not to
have money, no   That's just something
I see sometimes in the
problems with our manual life agents
.  The entity is small, the
employees
there are compartmentalized, they don't have any money.
But low and behold, the one over there is
her husband, Ferrer.  Well,
you know, you know, it's
like money.  So let's not
compartmentalize, my dear agents.  So
here we're just saying that you have
access even to the smallest
organization.  That's
our only point here, isn't that what we call group protection?
It caters to small medium
enterprises.  This is packaged meaning
there is a rate already.  So
automatically it will calculate for the
premium.  So if I tell Joy, how much do
I have to pay?  Ah, miss
owner, I know right away.  You can easily
present that.  So this is just a standard risk.
meaning predominantly they are office
based no and then what's good here are
three five options 100 200 300 400
and Php500,000
and up to Php300,000
auto covered no need to sign a
form so even if
the person is diabetic up to 300 we cover
even for 10 that up to 300 we cover 'is it
good another selling Peach.  Did you know
Mr.  Owner, where the owner is
a bit old, pretending to be a senior
.  Did you know Mr.  Owner we can
actually cover you up to 300,000
without submitting any insurance
ability.  So, sir, just saying that,
you've already tickled your brains.
You're tickled, no, and then you offer
another covering for him later on, no.
So this is our beauty.  It is a
package product therefore combonil.  The
basic plan includes life insurance,
accident, and TPTP.  And I think we are
already covering the three unforeseen
risks of life, of death, disability and
accident.  That's right.  So I wonder
if Mr. wouldn't be happy.  President.
My dear agency, uh, agents and leaders,
imagine if it were like this, this
cheap, so we can identify how
distinct, how unique, how useful this
product is.  From ages 18 to 40 years old,
only 256 needs to be paid per
employee.
This is for 100,000 per employee.
Or doesn't it sound like something like that
?  It's ringing that 100,000
coverage is only 256 for one whole year.   Do
we understand?  So if I
have 10 employees, 10,256,
as long as they are between 18 and 40 years old and they
are covered for 100,000 for life
and sorry life accident and EPTB.  And
then of course there are riders who
can only be options.  The beauty
here is that the
minimum premium requirement is only Php2,000.
So that means Php2,000.  So I have
five employees.  They need a total of
Php2,000.
So if not, let's add riders so
let's say 256 5, that's about 1,200 or something
.  Right?  But to
achieve 2,000, we'll add
primers.  Easy or easy to sell?
Easy to sell,
right?  So I said remember this
will make you penetrate in a small
entity make that initial step.  the foot
on the door the owner
congratulations you have a uh we have a
small bakery here how about covering the
ls of your employees no so who does
n't want to cover
their employees at a very minimal amount no and for
us in money no many of
us recognize this already they do
they do however some forget
that that's what sir is saying
the employees do
n't they so they know they can be
activated by group protect they know it's
easy to sell because small medium
enterprises can be easily issued because it's
possible
they know what they forget hey there's an
employee ha you got the masterl
Please do you know the age of those
they are entering the insurance age right?  So let's
not forget
that's the partnership that you know sir
has you know wanted me to say okay we
have a very good product line.  We have a
very good product in Manuel, but that's what we
get
from it because it can really
increase your sales.   Do
we understand?  Do you have
any questions about this particular product?
It's a stackage very easy to sell.  So,
nothing, nothing,
everything up to
Php300,000.  up to 300,000, then 400 and
500,000, we have simple and variety
.  Okay.
Okay.  Yes.  Only up to 64 really.
Yes.  Only up to 64 for this package
product.  For this package, let's say
the owner is 18, then
we will customize it.
We discussed it, okay?  Okay.  So here
we are.  So it's been one year, right?  1 year.
Yes.  So again, for us to make a
proposal here, all you need is your
birthday.  You need an occupation, of
course you need their name, so
that alone gives you an idea of
what Sir August is, he's the vice
president for HR, maybe he's around
100 small, maybe 50,000, maybe
there's something that can be set aside, again
my dear, the team is the team, let's not be
comportmentalize.  That's all
I'm saying.  Let's not
judge them, let's not be judgmental.
Yes.  Is it only possible for him to be in the company
or
yes, that's also possible.  He can also
but it will not call because it is already a
mixed group but anyway discuss later on.
But these are really employees, they should be for
group protection, employees in small groups.  Because you are
only 64 years old and the maximum is only up to 500
.  Later discussing later on
what we will do if
you say there are elderly people and then
those members you're increasing yeah, is the
number of employees in the
office increasing, for example to fall under this it
needs to be 80% yes the 20% can be those who are
not,
okay sorry I think this is what the
question is very what
When a company must be 80% covered
sir what is the standard but
we allow ah I said earlier predominantly
office so in the entire to the entire um
list to call under the group
protect 80%
their occupation must be standard meaning they are inside
the office including the messengers ah
can have a security guard there
we will allow them to be covered
as long as the substandard ones are only 20%
.
Oh okay.
Okay.
So we still pretty much have a lot to
cover.
Then, ma'am, it is written